<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>
<title>The Hodljuice Daily Pint</title>
<link>https://hodljuice.app</link>
<language>en-us</language>
<itunes:author>curated by Hodljuice</itunes:author>
<description>Daily collection of various Bitcoin-related podcasts</description>
<itunes:category text="Technology">
</itunes:category>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:owner>
<itunes:name>Hodljuice</itunes:name>
<itunes:email>hodljuice@hodljuice.app</itunes:email>
</itunes:owner>
<image>
<url>https://hodljuice.app/static/icon-512x512.png</url>
<title>The Hodljuice Daily Pint</title>
<link>https://hodljuice.app</link>
</image>
<lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 07:57:02 CST</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
        <title>Bitcoin and Markets: ETF Options Approval and Central Bankers Attack Bitcoin With Nonsense - E410</title>
        <itunes:author>Bitcoin and Markets</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>[ETF options, Central banking rhetoric, Macroeconomic analysis, Importance of research]</itunes:keywords>
        <description>This episode discusses ETF options approval and strategies used by central bankers to undermine Bitcoin. It analyzes macroeconomic factors affecting Bitcoin and critiques traditional financial institutions&#39; rhetoric. The episode stresses the importance of conducting independent research amidst financial misinformation.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/pscrb.fm/rss/p/traffic.libsyn.com/secure/bitcoinandmarkets/e410.mp3?dest-id=1230017" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-09-d6f410433ddde26b54a3bb5ce7e49c60</guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 07:57:02 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Bitcoin Audible: Chat 117-Bitcoin Threat Vectors on Final Settlement</title>
        <itunes:author>Bitcoin Audible</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>[Bitcoin custody, Security challenges, Multisig setups, Personal security incident]</itunes:keywords>
        <description>This episode covers Bitcoin custodial threat vectors and the unique security challenges associated with it. Insights from a personal security incident highlight the real risks faced by Bitcoin holders. The discussion includes the evolution of custody solutions and the importance of multisig setups for securing assets.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://episodes.castos.com/6626b866f2af87-36468692/1878430/c1e-q7pqji280p1f7n7d9-rkdk607gczg9-fiy2jf.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-09-363cca346c62d4476e09a04ed1398730</guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 07:57:02 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>BTC Sessions: WHY ARE WE BULLISH? David Branscum, Aladdin (BTC Cards), Nathan Fitzsimmons (The BTC Mentor) ep251</title>
        <itunes:author>BTC Sessions</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>[Bullish sentiment, Investment strategies, Self-custody, Hardware wallets]</itunes:keywords>
        <description>This episode features a discussion on the bullish sentiment surrounding Bitcoin, focusing on investment strategies and self-custody. Guests share their experiences with hardware wallets and the implications of Bitcoin&#39;s market behavior. The conversation emphasizes the importance of privacy and secure engagement with Bitcoin.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://anchor.fm/s/11e95d20/podcast/play/94169263/https%3A%2F%2Fd3ctxlq1ktw2nl.cloudfront.net%2Fstaging%2F2024-10-9%2Fddaa9f83-a2c4-85a4-8f74-9ae887ad37b9.m4a" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-09-f27b4663317cbb7541f07d29f73078d3</guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 07:57:02 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Coin Stories: &#39;News Block: Bitcoin Enters Price Discovery After Trump Win, Fed Cuts Rates Again, Bond Yields Rise Amid Inflation Fears&#39;</title>
        <itunes:author>Coin Stories</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>[Price discovery, Political impact, Institutional adoption, Economic trends]</itunes:keywords>
        <description>This episode covers critical news affecting Bitcoin, including its record highs following Trump&#39;s re-election and pro-crypto candidates winning congressional seats. It also discusses the Federal Reserve&#39;s rate cuts and their implications for Bitcoin alongside institutional adoption trends. The episode analyzes investment movements and Bitcoin&#39;s current economic environment.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://traffic.libsyn.com/secure/coinstories/307_61_NewsBlock_Nat.mp3?dest-id=2813255" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-09-7cf8945ac2ba3f0c051b07bd7d03b705</guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 07:57:02 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Fractal Bitcoin: Bitcoin 3rd day all-time highs! $420K in 2025?! Global FOMO incoming! - Ep.217</title>
        <itunes:author>Fractal Bitcoin</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>[Price discovery, ETF growth, Historical comparisons, Government adoption]</itunes:keywords>
        <description>This episode highlights Bitcoin&#39;s recent price activity, suggesting an ambitious price projection of $420,000 by 2025 amid a surge in ETF assets. It compares Bitcoin&#39;s adoption to the internet&#39;s growth and discusses significant developments in municipal acceptance of cryptocurrencies for tax payments. Noteworthy events include record purchases by Bitcoin ETFs.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://podcasts.captivate.fm/media/49a9d7c1-2716-4a9f-ac7b-7832619173d5/217-Fractal-Bitcoin-2024-11-08-Bitcoin-3rd-day-all-time-highs-4.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-09-aa796bad9f281d39002a298826e2a1cc</guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 07:57:02 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Onramp Media: &#39;The Last Trade E073: The Orange Wave with Larry Lepard &amp; David Foley&#39;</title>
        <itunes:author>Onramp Media</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>[Election impact, Bitcoin reserves, Monetary policy, Institutional strategies]</itunes:keywords>
        <description>This episode discusses the intersection of Bitcoin and upcoming election dynamics, emphasizing the potential for a pro-Bitcoin administration. Topics include the idea of a Strategic Bitcoin Reserve and the role of sound assets in today’s economy. The discussion includes market insights and comparisons between Bitcoin and gold.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://anchor.fm/s/e01a5d48/podcast/play/94144964/https%3A%2F%2Fd3ctxlq1ktw2nl.cloudfront.net%2Fstaging%2F2024-10-8%2F389471753-44100-2-dc2acdf376635.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-09-ab2254d1ac56507442131746132698a9</guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 07:57:02 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Pleb Underground: Bitcoin Mining CRISIS On The Horizon?</title>
        <itunes:author>Pleb Underground</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>[Bitcoin mining crisis, Cost implications, Resource allocation, Profitability concerns]</itunes:keywords>
        <description>This episode explores a looming crisis in Bitcoin mining as operational costs rise and profits decline. Hosts discuss resource shifts towards AI and the financial viability of Bitcoin mining operations. The discussion provides insights into current trends and challenges faced by miners in the cryptocurrency landscape.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://anchor.fm/s/add2abc4/podcast/play/94169424/https%3A%2F%2Fd3ctxlq1ktw2nl.cloudfront.net%2Fstaging%2F2024-10-9%2F389502020-44100-2-9158645eb7646.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-09-3fcc4e2a40fa721fb078c96ab2a86969</guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 07:57:02 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Robin Seyer: &#39;Trillion-Dollar BTC Bet: Microstrategy Soon Biggest Firm in the world?&#39;</title>
        <itunes:author>Robin Seyer</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>[MicroStrategy&#39;s Bitcoin strategy, Future of finance, Bitcoin as a commodity, Educational accessibility]</itunes:keywords>
        <description>Tim Kotzman discusses Bitcoin&#39;s transformative potential through MicroStrategy&#39;s significant investments, suggesting it could evolve into a trillion-dollar entity. The episode highlights Bitcoin as a commodity and emphasizes the need for accessible channels for engaging with cryptocurrency. It positions MicroStrategy at the forefront of Bitcoin&#39;s integration into the broader economy.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://anchor.fm/s/ed1174c8/podcast/play/93963409/https%3A%2F%2Fd3ctxlq1ktw2nl.cloudfront.net%2Fstaging%2F2024-10-4%2F389246724-44100-2-b067ffb217345.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-09-7579b366a568fd7b586553212a756117</guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 07:57:02 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Simply Bitcoin: &#39;BREAKING: Central Banker EXPOSED In BOMBSHELL Interview | EP 1115&#39;</title>
        <itunes:author>Simply Bitcoin</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>[Central banking policies, Monetary implications, Financial landscape, Inflation]</itunes:keywords>
        <description>This episode discusses controversial remarks made by Jerome Powell concerning central banking practices and their ramifications for the economy. The analysis focuses on the future of digital currencies and the implications of monetary policies on Bitcoin and inflationary concerns. This disclosure is contextualized against current economic challenges.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://anchor.fm/s/717a2198/podcast/play/94158233/https%3A%2F%2Fd3ctxlq1ktw2nl.cloudfront.net%2Fstaging%2F2024-10-8%2Fe85e7f81-f206-0540-74ad-aa5165431a58.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-09-e206ae5be87623a8c2dbaf2c8a1bdeaf</guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 07:57:02 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Swan Signal Live A Bitcoin Show: Is This the Start of a Super Cycle?</title>
        <itunes:author>Swan Signal Live A Bitcoin Show</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>[Market trends, Policy impact, Government support, Price projections]</itunes:keywords>
        <description>The discussion revolves around Bitcoin&#39;s performance following Trump&#39;s election, with a focus on potential new price highs and the possibility of a &quot;super cycle.&quot; It examines expected government policies favorable to Bitcoin, including potential strategic reserves. The episode captures a sense of optimism about Bitcoin&#39;s mainstream acceptance.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://cdn.simplecast.com/audio/6b4113f8-61fd-4976-a3e6-4d8ed2143233/episodes/66c8eb04-aad5-4762-a7e7-a6ff764b45a7/audio/7db6bc1b-31ed-4638-9ed1-87221b7150db/default_tc.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-09-6a6e060bcd4cf19752027aa289a579c5</guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 07:57:02 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>TFTC A Bitcoin Podcast: &#39;#554: UAP Disclosure Is Upon Us with Matt Pines&#39;</title>
        <itunes:author>TFTC A Bitcoin Podcast</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>[UAP disclosure, Bitcoin policy, Supranational institutions, Geopolitical insight]</itunes:keywords>
        <description>This episode with Matt Pines discusses the potential inclusion of Bitcoin in Trump&#39;s policy amidst an impending UAP disclosure. It covers the evolution of supranational financial institutions, American geopolitical power, and the implications of technology in current defense strategies. Key insights highlight the intersections between these areas and Bitcoin&#39;s future.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://anchor.fm/s/558f520/podcast/play/94118870/https%3A%2F%2Fd3ctxlq1ktw2nl.cloudfront.net%2Fstaging%2F2024-10-7%2F389439343-44100-2-9e27664ca37c4.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-09-1175a2dd9632d69e35355d44bf9ba245</guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 07:57:02 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>The Mark Moss Show: China Fires A Monetary Bazooka... Will It Be Enough?</title>
        <itunes:author>The Mark Moss Show</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>[China&#39;s financial strategy, Global market impact, Bitcoin implications, Investment strategies]</itunes:keywords>
        <description>Analyzing China&#39;s dramatic financial maneuvers, this episode questions the potential effects on global markets, including U.S. stocks and Bitcoin. Historical insights into past economic strategies provide context for current events. The discussion emphasizes the need for investment positioning in the wake of these developments.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://chtbl.com/track/5899E/podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/pscrb.fm/rss/p/traffic.omny.fm/d/clips/e73c998e-6e60-432f-8610-ae210140c5b1/7abcd9bc-1b66-4c1e-a89b-ae3c000322cc/58919d90-21e3-4fa0-8970-b22201811bef/audio.mp3?utm_source=Podcast&in_playlist=9acb2eb4-8765-4a8a-8a57-ae3c000322da" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-09-e02805fe36a4d20f0fce82e52ea7c107</guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 07:57:02 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>The Transformation of Value: What is Nuclear Energy with Nick Touran</title>
        <itunes:author>The Transformation of Value</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>[Nuclear energy, Political challenges, Economic implications, Regulatory landscape]</itunes:keywords>
        <description>This episode features a discussion with nuclear engineer Nick Touran about the challenges and opportunities facing the nuclear energy sector. The conversation covers the history of nuclear energy, its current regulatory issues, and the outlook for future technology in energy production and abundance.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://anchor.fm/s/d48d2ca8/podcast/play/94135276/https%3A%2F%2Fd3ctxlq1ktw2nl.cloudfront.net%2Fstaging%2F2024-10-8%2Fb7b6dca5-c70b-1184-8541-982ef2ce72b7.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-09-9321da2b50c1bbb1ce1477a449e1cbd0</guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 07:57:02 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>The What is Money Show: Can Trump Save the West? Freedom, Peterson vs. Dawkins, COVID &amp; Bitcoin w/ Bret Weinstein (WiM529)</title>
        <itunes:author>The What is Money Show</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>[Incentives in evolution, Libertarianism, Technology in academia, Freedom vs. tyranny]</itunes:keywords>
        <description>Dr. Bret Weinstein discusses the interplay of incentives in evolution and the relevance of Libertarianism to contemporary society, along with the potential impacts of Trump on freedom and governance. The dialogue explores major cultural debates, including the discourse surrounding COVID-19 mandates and their implications for societal values.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://cdn.simplecast.com/audio/2effec98-bec5-4728-ba08-7a86d776e682/episodes/fbe9659d-6735-4ccd-847b-7989b8eb4460/audio/ddd283fc-e95f-494d-a880-a57c48878ba2/default_tc.mp3?aid=rss_feed&feed=MLdpYXYI" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-09-820078ecbf5a2e8224037b2d5dad12ab</guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 07:57:02 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Token Metrics Daily Podcast: Rate Down, Crypto Up, BTC Tax📊</title>
        <itunes:author>Token Metrics Daily Podcast</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>[Fed rate decision, Crypto market response, Urban crypto adoption, Timeliness of information]</itunes:keywords>
        <description>This episode discusses the positive response of the crypto market to the US Federal Reserve&#39;s rate decision, alongside a focus on a US city significantly embracing cryptocurrency. The conversation highlights the role of crypto in improving public awareness of financial events.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://www.buzzsprout.com/2224561/episodes/16070362-rate-down-crypto-up-btc-tax.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-09-2028200e8b077474c23fdf429942979a</guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 07:57:02 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>
