<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>
<title>The Hodljuice Daily Pint</title>
<link>https://hodljuice.app</link>
<language>en-us</language>
<itunes:author>curated by Hodljuice</itunes:author>
<description>Daily collection of various Bitcoin-related podcasts</description>
<itunes:category text="Technology">
</itunes:category>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:owner>
<itunes:name>Hodljuice</itunes:name>
<itunes:email>hodljuice@hodljuice.app</itunes:email>
</itunes:owner>
<image>
<url>https://hodljuice.app/static/icon-512x512.png</url>
<title>The Hodljuice Daily Pint</title>
<link>https://hodljuice.app</link>
</image>
<lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 18:05:28 CST</lastBuildDate>
<item>
    <title>BitBuyBit: Take The Wins 🏆 | THE BITCOIN BRIEF 46</title>
    <itunes:author>BitBuyBit</itunes:author>
    <itunes:keywords>Bitcoin updates, Legal implications, Software tools, Community contributions</itunes:keywords>
    <description>This episode shares important updates in the bitcoin world, including the overturning of Tornado Cash sanctions and changes in prosecution. Notable updates on bitcoin utilities and tools such as Envoy and UmbrelOS are discussed, alongside community efforts to enhance user experience. Listeners are encouraged to support the show through contributions.</description>
    <enclosure url="" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-12-05-5fece834664ee5c1ca2d1ef2c81c03df</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 18:05:29 CST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Bitcoin And: $100,000 Bitcoin</title>
    <itunes:author>Bitcoin And</itunes:author>
    <itunes:keywords>Bitcoin valuation, Market perceptions, Political commentary, Ordinals</itunes:keywords>
    <description>This episode discusses the changing perceptions of Bitcoin, including its rise to $100,000, and the use of ordinals in securing important documents. It highlights Trump&#39;s proclamation of credit for Bitcoin&#39;s growth, alongside central banks’ waning interest in CBDCs. The discussion also touches on philosophical themes related to reality.</description>
    <enclosure url="" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-12-05-58c7e0d09bea2282b213125ca68178e1</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 18:05:29 CST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Bitcoin Veterans: Bitcoin Veterans Spaces, Putin &quot;Who can ban bitcoin? Nobody&quot;</title>
    <itunes:author>Bitcoin Veterans</itunes:author>
    <itunes:keywords>Cryptocurrency regulation, Political discourse, Bitcoin resilience, Global perspective</itunes:keywords>
    <description>The episode examines Vladimir Putin&#39;s statements regarding Bitcoin regulation, discussing the resilient nature of Bitcoin in light of potential bans. It highlights the global landscape of cryptocurrency and the importance of Bitcoin amidst current economic challenges.</description>
    <enclosure url="" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-12-05-040d6b29bbe405579f9ed33ff9f4d8e0</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 18:05:29 CST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Bitcoin Veterans: Bitcoin Veterans Spaces with Eric Yakes</title>
    <itunes:author>Bitcoin Veterans</itunes:author>
    <itunes:keywords>Bitcoin market, Investment strategies, Community engagement, Advocacy</itunes:keywords>
    <description>In this episode, Eric Yakes shares insights on Bitcoin investment strategies and the market&#39;s future. The conversation emphasizes the importance of community involvement and advocacy in promoting Bitcoin adoption.</description>
    <enclosure url="" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-12-05-b7f5968314fbbd345bee8a0454cef660</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 18:05:29 CST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Bitcoin Veterans: Bitcoin Veterans Spaces, Black Rock 500k BTC</title>
    <itunes:author>Bitcoin Veterans</itunes:author>
    <itunes:keywords>Institutional investment, Market trends, Bitcoin analytics, Retail impact</itunes:keywords>
    <description>The hosts analyze Black Rock&#39;s recent activities related to Bitcoin and their implications for the market. This episode explores how institutional participation may affect retail investors and future market growth opportunities in the cryptocurrency space.</description>
    <enclosure url="" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-12-05-5dbca3cb5bdaa7c93603c40c2c686316</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 18:05:29 CST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Bitcoin for Millennials: Meet the Banking Veteran who is all in on Bitcoin | Caitlin Long | BFM105</title>
    <itunes:author>Bitcoin for Millennials</itunes:author>
    <itunes:keywords>Digital banking, Regulatory landscape, Bitcoin adoption, Financial transitions</itunes:keywords>
    <description>Caitlin Long discusses her experiences in finance and her advocacy for Bitcoin integration within traditional banking. The episode covers challenges posed by outdated banking systems and the importance of understanding regulatory issues surrounding Bitcoin adoption.</description>
    <enclosure url="" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-12-05-20460dac682df2c9986ac22cf001b16f</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 18:05:29 CST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Coin Stories: News Block: Bitcoin Hits $100K! Powell on Bitcoin vs Gold, Trump’s SEC Pick &amp; BRICS Tariff Threat, MicroStrategy’s $312M Daily Stack</title>
    <itunes:author>Coin Stories</itunes:author>
    <itunes:keywords>Bitcoin market updates, Regulatory developments, High-profile investments, Global finance</itunes:keywords>
    <description>This episode covers significant news as Bitcoin reaches the $100,000 mark and highlights Jerome Powell&#39;s dismissal of Bitcoin as a store of value. The discussion includes Trump’s nomination of a new SEC Chair and MicroStrategy’s major Bitcoin purchases.</description>
    <enclosure url="" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-12-05-db4a1401372169d753f3941c9c968d7c</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 18:05:29 CST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Fractal Bitcoin: Bitcoin Surpasses $100K!!! Bitcoiners Still Stacking With Gratitude. Insane Adoption - Ep.226</title>
    <itunes:author>Fractal Bitcoin</itunes:author>
    <itunes:keywords>Market milestones, Bitcoin community, Geopolitical perspectives, Adoption trends</itunes:keywords>
    <description>The hosts celebrate Bitcoin surpassing $100,000 while discussing ongoing commitment to accumulate Bitcoin. The episode emphasizes reflections on key figures in the community and significant geopolitical statements affecting Bitcoin&#39;s future.</description>
    <enclosure url="" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-12-05-26fefbf84a0da28ac595596e392757f4</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 18:05:29 CST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Galaxy Brains: Is This Time Different? w/ Sam Callahan</title>
    <itunes:author>Galaxy Brains</itunes:author>
    <itunes:keywords>Market analysis, Bitcoin dynamics, Influential figures</itunes:keywords>
    <description>Alex Thorn invites Sam Callahan to analyze Bitcoin markets and discusses the impact of MicroStrategy and the Trump administration on cryptocurrency dynamics.</description>
    <enclosure url="" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-12-05-35db2841597d69e35b8644ea93381b1f</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 18:05:29 CST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Pleb Underground: Aviation Company To Mine Bitcoin!</title>
    <itunes:author>Pleb Underground</itunes:author>
    <itunes:keywords>Innovation in mining, Industry disruptions, Historical comparisons</itunes:keywords>
    <description>The episode explores an aviation company&#39;s new venture into Bitcoin mining, drawing parallels to the dot-com bubble. The hosts discuss the company&#39;s plans and challenges within the evolving relationship between aviation and cryptocurrency.</description>
    <enclosure url="" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-12-05-756f2748fe4d90641c498c03ebe15f9b</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 18:05:29 CST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Rabbit Hole Recap: &#39;$100K BITCOIN | RABBIT HOLE RECAP #334&#39;</title>
    <itunes:author>Rabbit Hole Recap</itunes:author>
    <itunes:keywords>Market milestones, Regulatory updates, Current events</itunes:keywords>
    <description>The episode discusses Bitcoin reaching the $100,000 milestone and its implications for the market. Key updates on regulatory engagements and product launches related to Bitcoin are also featured.</description>
    <enclosure url="" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-12-05-5ac11c3d10fdca9b7781af2153dbb557</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 18:05:29 CST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Robin Seyer: &#39;Parker Lewis: In 10 Years EVERYBODY will use Bitcoin as money!&#39;</title>
    <itunes:author>Robin Seyer</itunes:author>
    <itunes:keywords>Adoption curve, Fiat currency dynamics, Psychological factors</itunes:keywords>
    <description>Parker Lewis discusses the gradual understanding of Bitcoin&#39;s value leading to widespread adoption. The episode emphasizes how fiat currency failures may drive adoption and highlights Bitcoin&#39;s potential as a medium of exchange.</description>
    <enclosure url="" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-12-05-c5ef13effc4271853338ccee80694c2d</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 18:05:29 CST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Simply Bitcoin: &#39;Bitcoin JUST Hit $100k: $13M is The Next Milestone | EP 1133&#39;</title>
    <itunes:author>Simply Bitcoin</itunes:author>
    <itunes:keywords>Bitcoin valuations, Market predictions, Economic significance</itunes:keywords>
    <description>Michael Saylor discusses the implications of Bitcoin hitting $100,000 and introduces a new milestone of $13 million. The episode provides insights into current trends and future potential within the cryptocurrency landscape.</description>
    <enclosure url="" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-12-05-ce9093eaf0736c9eb4280abc5cf603f0</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 18:05:29 CST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Stephan Livera Podcast: The Evolution of Alby with Michael Bumann | SLP622</title>
    <itunes:author>Stephan Livera Podcast</itunes:author>
    <itunes:keywords>Technology integration, User experience, Lightning network</itunes:keywords>
    <description>The episode explores the evolution of Alby as it transitions to a self-custodial Lightning wallet. Discussion includes security considerations, user experience challenges, and the role of various service providers in enhancing Bitcoin services.</description>
    <enclosure url="" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-12-05-a6d5a1111241b88834a1b76fd5bf0bd8</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 18:05:29 CST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Bitcoin Infinity Show: &#39;The Future of Bitcoin Mining with General Kenobi - Bitcoin Infinity Show #137&#39;</title>
    <itunes:author>Bitcoin Infinity Show</itunes:author>
    <itunes:keywords>Bitcoin mining trends, Industry forecasts, Profitability challenges</itunes:keywords>
    <description>General Kenobi, a Bitcoin mining expert, shares insights on the future of Bitcoin mining, including the potential decline in profitability. The episode discusses emerging trends and critical changes in the Bitcoin mining landscape.</description>
    <enclosure url="" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-12-05-fa277399bb6b1e3b05b10f604ebb651c</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 18:05:29 CST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
    <title>The Breakdown: &#39;BTC at $100,000: The Bitcoin Era Begins&#39;</title>
    <itunes:author>The Breakdown</itunes:author>
    <itunes:keywords>Market milestones, Economic implications, Cryptocurrency transition</itunes:keywords>
    <description>NLW recaps the significant occasion of Bitcoin reaching $100,000, sharing insights on the broader implications for both the cryptocurrency market and the economy.</description>
    <enclosure url="" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-12-05-27c19f79b1871f857196c2b8cae39d37</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 18:05:29 CST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
    <title>The Breakdown: Crypto Ally Paul Atkins To Be Named SEC Chair</title>
    <itunes:author>The Breakdown</itunes:author>
    <itunes:keywords>Regulatory landscape, Industry perspectives, SEC challenges</itunes:keywords>
    <description>The episode discusses Trump’s selection of Paul Atkins as the new SEC Chair, analyzing potential challenges ahead for the crypto industry, particularly within the framework set by the previous chair.</description>
    <enclosure url="" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-12-05-80092860e64239f61035ef028ae08adc</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 18:05:29 CST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
    <title>The Bugle Weekly: Shinobi is Hot | Behind the Podcast Episode 2</title>
    <itunes:author>The Bugle Weekly</itunes:author>
    <itunes:keywords>Cultural analysis, Storytelling, Character significance</itunes:keywords>
    <description>The hosts discuss the character of Shinobi and his significance in storytelling, examining the cultural impact and evolution of ninjas in various narratives. Listener insights are shared to enhance the discussion.</description>
    <enclosure url="" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-12-05-9d754cdc6fcdd1f289d9abb1445e33ac</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 18:05:29 CST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Canadian Bitcoiners Podcast: The CBP - The ₿roken Ruler - Talking About MicroStrategy</title>
    <itunes:author>Canadian Bitcoiners Podcast</itunes:author>
    <itunes:keywords>Bitcoin economics, Market impacts, Canadian perspective</itunes:keywords>
    <description>This episode focuses on the significance of MicroStrategy in the Bitcoin ecosystem, exploring how Bitcoin is expected to impact Canada’s economic landscape. The discussion emphasizes that none of the information should be considered financial advice.</description>
    <enclosure url="" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-12-05-884823fdc20d64664be45f04ed5ce1f5</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 18:05:29 CST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
    <title>The Mark Moss Show: Is Bitcoin Really Safe For Your Wealth? | Garrett &quot;GMONEY&quot;</title>
    <itunes:author>The Mark Moss Show</itunes:author>
    <itunes:keywords>Wealth protection, Financial empowerment, Political commentary</itunes:keywords>
    <description>Mark discusses wealth protection strategies with Garrett &quot;G-Money,&quot; focusing on Bitcoin&#39;s role in reclaiming financial control amid challenging political climates. The episode presents actionable frameworks designed to empower listeners.</description>
    <enclosure url="" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-12-05-8a2c0746194e95c330a56112a26a8919</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 18:05:29 CST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Ungovernable Misfits: Take The Wins 🏆 | THE BITCOIN BRIEF 46</title>
    <itunes:author>Ungovernable Misfits</itunes:author>
    <itunes:keywords>Bitcoin updates, Legal implications, Software tools, Community contributions</itunes:keywords>
    <description>This episode shares important updates in the bitcoin world, including the overturning of Tornado Cash sanctions and changes in prosecution. Notable updates on bitcoin utilities and tools such as Envoy and UmbrelOS are discussed, alongside community efforts to enhance user experience. Listeners are encouraged to support the show through contributions.</description>
    <enclosure url="" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-12-05-a32f2de51cd88b91d6b1b7ec5af4c4fc</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 18:05:29 CST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
    <title>What Bitcoin Did: WBD IS BACK - $100K BITCOIN, MICROSTRATEGY AND THE BULL MARKET w/ Checkmate</title>
    <itunes:author>What Bitcoin Did</itunes:author>
    <itunes:keywords>Market analysis, Institutional demand, Strategic investments</itunes:keywords>
    <description>Checkmate discusses the relaunch of &quot;What Bitcoin Did&quot; while addressing Bitcoin breaking the $100,000 mark and the growth in institutional demand. The conversation includes the Strategic Bitcoin Reserve and options&#39; impacts on market dynamics.</description>
    <enclosure url="" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
    <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-12-05-74da3df5f1564816d6dbd6560d0ccf2d</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 18:05:29 CST</pubDate>
</item>
    <item>
        <title>Bitcorner with Juan Cienfuegos: &quot;Khushboo Khullar: About Adopting Bitcoin, Lightning Ventures, and Thunder Funder&quot;</title>
        <itunes:author>Bitcorner with Juan Cienfuegos</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>Bitcoin adoption, startup funding, Lightning Ventures, community connections</itunes:keywords>
        <description>Khushboo Khullar from Lightning Ventures discusses the importance of Bitcoin adoption and its effect on global acceptance. She explores the platform Thunder Funder, which aims to democratize investments in Bitcoin startups. The episode also highlights the relationship between Bitcoin, energy security, and nation-state reserves. Khushboo shares her personal journey and the significance of community in the Bitcoin ecosystem.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://api.substack.com/feed/podcast/152400929/f3657d19975677c5a6d027a475310cb1.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-12-03-2d8964ff2baf92e75162256a2078f672</guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 20:36:35 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Coin Stories: &#39;Luke Gromen: Bitcoin as &quot;The New Oil,&quot; Trump&amp;#39;s Tariffs, and the Death of the Dollar-Centric System&#39;</title>
        <itunes:author>Coin Stories</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>Macro economics, Bitcoin valuation, geopolitical implications, Trump&#39;s economic policies</itunes:keywords>
        <description>In this episode, Luke Gromen shares his macroeconomic outlook and discusses the implications of Bitcoin being considered &quot;the new oil.&quot; He covers topics such as Trump&#39;s economic strategies, the strengthening dollar, and Bitcoin&#39;s potential as a strategic asset. The conversation also addresses how tariffs are affecting global markets and hints at Bitcoin’s massive potential for future growth.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://traffic.libsyn.com/secure/coinstories/315_Luke_Gromen.mp3?dest-id=2813255" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-12-03-299d54e86f02f4ff4c657bede12a14ce</guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 20:36:35 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Fractal Bitcoin: Bitcoin Update! Pump Soon. US Dollar Collapse Update! BlackRock’s 500,000 BTC - Ep. 225</title>
        <itunes:author>Fractal Bitcoin</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>Bitcoin price predictions, ETF developments, digital currency concerns, investment security</itunes:keywords>
        <description>This episode anticipates a surge in Bitcoin&#39;s price and discusses the recent milestone where a spot ETF has exceeded 500,000 Bitcoin in assets under management. The conversation includes Virgin Voyages becoming a pioneer in Bitcoin payment acceptance and the risks associated with increased government involvement in cryptocurrency. Listeners are urged to secure their Bitcoin outside exchanges.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://podcasts.captivate.fm/media/bdb1b0c9-700e-44c0-ac3b-3569e7bb4af1/225-Fractal-Bitcoin-2024-12-03-Bitcoin-Update-Pump-Soon-US-Doll.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-12-03-68e196bcc8710f011c11c45385506566</guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 20:36:35 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Pleb Underground: The FIRST Bitcoin Bear Market Indicators of This Cycle</title>
        <itunes:author>Pleb Underground</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>Market cycles, investment indicators, Bitcoin&#39;s future, financial advice</itunes:keywords>
        <description>The episode discusses early indicators of an impending Bitcoin bear market, cautioning listeners against complacency despite current bullish trends. Essential topics include potential downturns, implications of pending legislation, and the consequences of the Federal Reserve&#39;s interest rate adjustments. The hosts advise staying informed and vigilant as market conditions change.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://anchor.fm/s/add2abc4/podcast/play/95258750/https%3A%2F%2Fd3ctxlq1ktw2nl.cloudfront.net%2Fstaging%2F2024-11-2%2F390849970-44100-2-8e692597b3a31.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-12-03-4cde82e3e2588b6578f67ed859004813</guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 20:36:35 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Robin Seyer: &#39;The Big Investment Lie: Why Bitcoin is Your Only Choice!&#39;</title>
        <itunes:author>Robin Seyer</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>Behavioral analysis, autism and finance, delayed gratification, barriers to Bitcoin adoption</itunes:keywords>
        <description>Dillon Ganesh discusses the intersection of behavioral analysis and Bitcoin, emphasizing the importance of saving and the role of delayed gratification in financial success. He addresses common misconceptions about Bitcoin and the barriers to its adoption, advocating for education and understanding its value. The episode envisions a future where Bitcoin empowers individuals through financial security.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://anchor.fm/s/ed1174c8/podcast/play/95177641/https%3A%2F%2Fd3ctxlq1ktw2nl.cloudfront.net%2Fstaging%2F2024-10-30%2F390752682-44100-2-89ead7327c235.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-12-03-1b12f4804b9f17580c6b63028c22dd30</guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 20:36:35 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Simply Bitcoin: Will Bitcoin Make Microsoft the Next Microstrategy? | EP 1131</title>
        <itunes:author>Simply Bitcoin</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>Corporate Bitcoin strategy, financial implications, market perception, risk assessment</itunes:keywords>
        <description>The hosts explore the potential for Microsoft to adopt a Bitcoin acquisition strategy similar to Microstrategy, analyzing the financial motivations and market implications. They discuss the risks and rewards involved in such a strategic move, highlighting the effect on both corporations and the cryptocurrency market. The conversation emphasizes Bitcoin&#39;s growing importance in corporate financial planning.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://anchor.fm/s/717a2198/podcast/play/95313065/https%3A%2F%2Fd3ctxlq1ktw2nl.cloudfront.net%2Fstaging%2F2024-11-3%2F71e1593c-e044-95e0-2657-f0d9eee69aa4.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-12-03-8420c2c084d5717537d5ec3c4714f22d</guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 20:36:35 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>The Bitcoin Frontier: What happens after $100,000 bitcoin? Willy Woo’s first interview in 3 years</title>
        <itunes:author>The Bitcoin Frontier</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>Bitcoin market analysis, institutional impact, energy scarcity, geopolitical implications</itunes:keywords>
        <description>Willy Woo provides an insightful analysis of the Bitcoin market, discussing the influence of major players like MicroStrategy and BlackRock. He outlines Bitcoin’s potential to become a global reserve asset, its energy scarcity model, and how new accounting standards could impact corporate holdings. The episode explores Bitcoin&#39;s role in reshaping global monetary systems and geopolitical landscapes.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/a81291c0/296365f8.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-12-03-4edd841fa42553260a45a25087285811</guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 20:36:35 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>The Bitcoin Standard Podcast: 250. Fiat Architecture and Time Preference</title>
        <itunes:author>The Bitcoin Standard Podcast</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>Economic behavior, fiat currency influence, time preference</itunes:keywords>
        <description>In this episode, the discussion revolves around how fiat currency shapes societal structure and individual economic behavior through its effects on time preference. The guests analyze the implications of easy money on architecture and broader economic systems. The conversation critiques current monetary policies and emphasizes the need for alternative models.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://www.buzzsprout.com/1849151/episodes/16213100-250-fiat-architecture-and-time-preference.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-12-03-aa845cdb59084a56a55ded6ee6fcb805</guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 20:36:35 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>The Block Reward Bitcoin For Beginners: &#39;62: Ryan Macleod ON: The Synergy Of Bitcoin Mining and Nuclear Power&#39;</title>
        <itunes:author>The Block Reward Bitcoin For Beginners</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>Nuclear energy, Bitcoin mining integration, energy challenges, technological advancements</itunes:keywords>
        <description>Ryan MacLeod discusses the synergy between Bitcoin mining and nuclear power, highlighting how nuclear energy could meet Bitcoin’s energy demands and benefit power grids. The discussion includes challenges, opportunities in public perception, and advancements in both sectors. He also discusses the concept of transforming waste energy into value through Bitcoin mining.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://audio-delivery.cohostpodcasting.com/audio/99707283-ab68-4240-9fff-177a3f522270/episodes/328609ab-b7e7-40b6-939b-da6155b97f06/episode.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-12-03-93f64022fa95f37012c425967552bb9e</guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 20:36:35 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>The Mining Pod: Block’s New ASIC Miner With Core Scientific and Proto</title>
        <itunes:author>The Mining Pod</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>ASIC mining technology, industry collaboration, market dynamics, geopolitical factors</itunes:keywords>
        <description>In this episode, The Mining Pod discusses the collaboration between Proto and Core Scientific on new ASIC chip technology designed for Bitcoin mining. The hosts cover the advantages of developing ASICs, the competitive landscape of the industry, and geopolitical influences affecting the market. The episode also explores future technological advancements and market interests in US-made ASICs.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/SSYDL1642390558.mp3?updated=1733194818" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-12-03-3115053f9953b9785242021db80dfe11</guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 20:36:35 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>The Mining Pod: Cleanspark FY2024 Earnings Call Analysis</title>
        <itunes:author>The Mining Pod</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>Financial performance, market trends, bitcoin mining stocks</itunes:keywords>
        <description>This episode analyzes Cleanspark&#39;s FY2024 earnings call, with insights from analysts on the company’s financial performance and its implications for the Bitcoin mining industry. The discussion covers key market trends impacting mining stocks and includes expert opinions from industry leaders. Listeners are encouraged to find more details on these insights through additional platforms.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/SSYDL5100484438.mp3?updated=1733193944" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-12-03-71987139a69d54f5b13b8d4a35f95376</guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 20:36:35 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>The What is Money Show: Breaking Out of the Money Printing Mind Control with Dad Saves America (WiM536)</title>
        <itunes:author>The What is Money Show</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>Inflation critique, Keynesian economics, integrity in finance, familial perspectives</itunes:keywords>
        <description>John Papola discusses the nature of money, criticizing the inflationary practices inherent in current economic systems and equating money printing to mind control. He examines how these economic policies affect societal integrity and the significance of fatherhood in modern discourse. The episode critiques Keynesian economics and emphasizes the importance of responsible financial practices.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://cdn.simplecast.com/audio/2effec98-bec5-4728-ba08-7a86d776e682/episodes/cc53ba42-2658-49bb-8b85-5d9b5c293fe6/audio/8ec1c24e-ff2a-4afd-a2bd-e922c408d1b4/default_tc.mp3?aid=rss_feed&feed=MLdpYXYI" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-12-03-4c330eb18481514bcfed2e8b3052d4ec</guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 20:36:35 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>
