<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>
<title>The Hodljuice Daily Pint</title>
<link>https://hodljuice.app</link>
<language>en-us</language>
<itunes:author>curated by Hodljuice</itunes:author>
<description>Daily collection of various Bitcoin-related podcasts</description>
<itunes:category text="Technology">
</itunes:category>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:owner>
<itunes:name>Hodljuice</itunes:name>
<itunes:email>hodljuice@hodljuice.app</itunes:email>
</itunes:owner>
<image>
<url>https://hodljuice.app/static/icon-512x512.png</url>
<title>The Hodljuice Daily Pint</title>
<link>https://hodljuice.app</link>
</image>
<lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 18:04:53 CST</lastBuildDate>

    <item>
        <title>Bit Buy Bit: Unlocking Cultural Capital with Bitcoin | The Confab 12: Rev Hodl</title>
        <itunes:author>Bit Buy Bit</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords></itunes:keywords>
        <description>Rev Hodl discusses creating a self-sustaining, circular economy based on Bitcoin at his Michigan homestead, integrating practices like rabbit farming and cannabis cultivation. He emphasizes the importance of building a local Bitcoin community and critiques KYC systems to promote resilience within Bitcoin communities. The episode highlights permaculture principles along with fostering cultural capital. </description>
        <enclosure url="https://op3.dev/e/serve.podhome.fm/episode/df3c7f87-bdab-41fe-1438-08dbf068e250/6386666189545195252956c0c0-b902-4843-99dc-08941f63913bv2.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-12-703b0badd0ab2b1a59c8d1aa93718a60</guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 21:14:45 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Bitcoin and Markets: Bitcoin Momentum is Surging - Weekly Roundup! - E412</title>
        <itunes:author>Bitcoin and Markets</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords></itunes:keywords>
        <description>This episode explores the current momentum in the Bitcoin market amidst various macroeconomic factors, money trends, and geopolitical developments. The host analyses recent news affecting Bitcoin and significant market trends to watch. Listeners are encouraged to stay engaged with these evolving dynamics. </description>
        <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/pscrb.fm/rss/p/traffic.libsyn.com/secure/bitcoinandmarkets/e412.mp3?dest-id=1230017" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-12-300286f9c8c63529c2e9f9566f789bb6</guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 21:14:45 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Bitcoin Veterans: Bitcoin Veterans SITREP: $84k Bitcoin</title>
        <itunes:author>Bitcoin Veterans</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords></itunes:keywords>
        <description>The hosts discuss Bitcoin&#39;s recent price surge to $84k, analyzing key market trends and regulatory changes impacting Bitcoin&#39;s trajectory. They provide insights into investor sentiments and potential future developments as the market evolves. </description>
        <enclosure url="https://anchor.fm/s/e3cb8764/podcast/play/94307209/https%3A%2F%2Fd3ctxlq1ktw2nl.cloudfront.net%2Fstaging%2F2024-10-12%2Fb8a71877-f450-80d7-96fe-cb08bdec6d89.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-12-8c5a2720f82371392194d961f17951a2</guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 21:14:45 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Bitcoin Veterans: Bitcoin Veterans Space with MARA $74k BTC</title>
        <itunes:author>Bitcoin Veterans</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords></itunes:keywords>
        <description>This episode features a Twitter space discussion with MARA on Bitcoin&#39;s price reaching $74k. The dialogue covers market dynamics, community responses, and predictions fueled by institutional buying and technological advancements in the Bitcoin network. </description>
        <enclosure url="https://anchor.fm/s/e3cb8764/podcast/play/94307122/https%3A%2F%2Fd3ctxlq1ktw2nl.cloudfront.net%2Fstaging%2F2024-10-12%2F0f80e258-b507-282f-0b5f-ae244b4dfbdf.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-12-09b01dda2e59792667087a2d16c98468</guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 21:14:45 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Fractal Bitcoin: Bitcoin $90,000!!! Momentum STRONG, everyone’s buying, Who is selling now??</title>
        <itunes:author>Fractal Bitcoin</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords></itunes:keywords>
        <description>In this episode, the hosts discuss Bitcoin&#39;s record daily movement and strong market momentum, leading towards a potential bull run. They explore institutional interest, large acquisitions, and the implications of recent developments for future price movements. The conversation highlights significant market indicators and societal engagement with Bitcoin. </description>
        <enclosure url="https://podcasts.captivate.fm/media/b140dc71-4b26-4fc7-83b4-a39582a37b86/219-Fractal-Bitcoin-2024-11-12-Bitcoin-90-000-Momentum-STRONG-e.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-12-7a426672d3d5927e218a7f39faec00b8</guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 21:14:45 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Onramp Media: Wake Up Call (11.12.24): Kristin Stroud &amp; Matt McClintock</title>
        <itunes:author>Onramp Media</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>Themes:</itunes:keywords>
        <description>The &quot;Wake Up Call&quot; show aims to educate financial professionals about Bitcoin&#39;s investment thesis and its potential to disrupt legacy financial services. Hosted by experts in traditional markets, the episode encourages listeners to embrace Bitcoin and provides insights into navigating this evolving landscape. Guests share their personal journeys with Bitcoin, fostering practical knowledge. </description>
        <enclosure url="https://anchor.fm/s/e01a5d48/podcast/play/94320933/https%3A%2F%2Fd3ctxlq1ktw2nl.cloudfront.net%2Fstaging%2F2024-10-12%2F389692041-44100-2-5da7829a86bbe.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-12-67c1fc2d0dc43cea1ebb7bda08dced9f</guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 21:14:45 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Pleb Underground: THE GREAT WEALTH TRANSFER is here! Are You Ready?</title>
        <itunes:author>Pleb Underground</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords></itunes:keywords>
        <description>Discussing the ongoing Bitcoin bull run, the episode examines the significance for Bitcoiners and those skeptical about its momentum. Insights from figures like Adam Back and research on wealth transfer describe the urgency for new investments in Bitcoin while warning against being passive. </description>
        <enclosure url="https://anchor.fm/s/add2abc4/podcast/play/94285148/https%3A%2F%2Fd3ctxlq1ktw2nl.cloudfront.net%2Fstaging%2F2024-10-12%2F389644957-44100-2-d6be4babd9aa1.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-12-9c5cb3ebd8664527403e259a5045d8d0</guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 21:14:45 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Robin Seyr: ALL-IN on Bitcoin: The Moment That Changed Everything!</title>
        <itunes:author>Robin Seyr</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords></itunes:keywords>
        <description>Scott Lindberg discusses the transformative effects of Bitcoin on personal lives and community engagement, emphasizing its potential as a new game with better incentives. He addresses the challenges in educating non-Bitcoiners and explores the cultural shifts associated with Bitcoin, highlighting hope and entrepreneurial spirit. </description>
        <enclosure url="https://anchor.fm/s/ed1174c8/podcast/play/94083942/https%3A%2F%2Fd3ctxlq1ktw2nl.cloudfront.net%2Fstaging%2F2024-10-7%2F389396948-44100-2-f12029544680b.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-12-9f9aadac661141772840931a25b7f1ce</guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 21:14:45 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>SimplyBitcoin: Why Bitcoin Reaching $850k is Inevitable (Explained) | EP 1117</title>
        <itunes:author>SimplyBitcoin</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords></itunes:keywords>
        <description>The episode discusses Bitcoin&#39;s ascent as it surpasses the market cap of silver and predicts its inevitable rise above gold and real estate. The hosts explore the implications of these developments and analyze factors contributing to Bitcoin&#39;s forward momentum within financial landscapes. </description>
        <enclosure url="https://anchor.fm/s/717a2198/podcast/play/94335239/https%3A%2F%2Fd3ctxlq1ktw2nl.cloudfront.net%2Fstaging%2F2024-10-13%2F155a1f7f-de38-8f65-e00b-a271354e6a4f.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-12-9a56d22cc7e8bf17d779357b2e82047b</guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 21:14:45 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>The Bitcoin Frontier: Protecting your own strategic bitcoin reserve for 100+ years with Joe Kelly</title>
        <itunes:author>The Bitcoin Frontier</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords></itunes:keywords>
        <description>Joe Kelly of Unchained discusses the significance of self-custody in Bitcoin, sharing his personal journey and the founding vision of his company. The episode dives into challenges for Bitcoin adoption globally and the importance of developing secure strategies for long-term Bitcoin management. </description>
        <enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/2df61efb/8b1f3bb8.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-12-7c8101ffb8d93d9fa2432e52aee98e7f</guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 21:14:45 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>The Bitcoin Standard Podcast: 247. Can Interest Rates Fall to Zero on the Free Market</title>
        <itunes:author>The Bitcoin Standard Podcast</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords></itunes:keywords>
        <description>Dr. Saifedean Ammous presents a historical perspective on interest rates and proposes a theory on how they can diminish in a free market with hard money. His insights were shared at a conference focused on property and economic principles. </description>
        <enclosure url="https://www.buzzsprout.com/1849151/episodes/16090369-247-can-interest-rates-fall-to-zero-on-the-free-market.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-12-d3d05b988d0329b1efbee56ba4553b15</guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 21:14:45 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>The Block Reward Bitcoin For Beginners: 59: Michael Dunworth ON: Bitcoin is a Cheat Code</title>
        <itunes:author>The Block Reward Bitcoin For Beginners</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords></itunes:keywords>
        <description>Michael Dunworth argues that Bitcoin serves as a &quot;cheat code&quot; for resolving global financial challenges, discussing its implications for institutional adoption and potential regulatory pressures. The episode addresses the broader impact Bitcoin can have on corporations and economic strategies. </description>
        <enclosure url="https://audio-delivery.cohostpodcasting.com/audio/99707283-ab68-4240-9fff-177a3f522270/episodes/91f36c15-5f84-4287-9c41-2fd07ac23ea0/episode.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-12-5299c31cb054f785e1f0a20a6418045c</guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 21:14:45 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>The Breakdown: BTC Hits $90,000 as Animal Spirits Return</title>
        <itunes:author>The Breakdown</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords></itunes:keywords>
        <description>Covering Bitcoin&#39;s remarkable surge past $90,000, the episode focuses on the return of investor enthusiasm and its implications for the market. NLW emphasizes the broader context of this price movement and what it signals for the future of Bitcoin investments.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://traffic.megaphone.fm/BWG1418209762.mp3?updated=1731466434" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-12-45b21f8a6ead0806bce69dd9bbf751a7</guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 21:14:45 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>The Canadian Bitcoiners Podcast: The CBP #189 (Bitcoin News Stories) - New ATH and F U</title>
        <itunes:author>The Canadian Bitcoiners Podcast</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords></itunes:keywords>
        <description>This episode provides an analysis of recent Bitcoin news, particularly the new all-time high, with a focus on implications for Canadian audiences. The hosts reflect on the evolving landscape of Bitcoin, emphasizing regulatory issues and community perspectives on Bitcoin adoption. </description>
        <enclosure url="https://anchor.fm/s/538d43f4/podcast/play/94302564/https%3A%2F%2Fd3ctxlq1ktw2nl.cloudfront.net%2Fstaging%2F2024-10-12%2F906880a3-ac82-23f4-cdb8-25b437c798f5.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-12-be05c8f90e6f646c13688aca3dea86b3</guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 21:14:45 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>The Mining Pod Bitcoin Mining News: Bitcoin Mining Capital Markets, How the Elections Benefit BTC with Mostafa Al-Mashita</title>
        <itunes:author>The Mining Pod Bitcoin Mining News</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords></itunes:keywords>
        <description>Mostafa Al-Mashita discusses recent improvements in Bitcoin mining capital markets, the complexities of accessing debt, and implications of a potential Trump presidency. The episode examines various financial products and market conditions that affect miners and their operations. </description>
        <enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/SSYDL9728684873.mp3?updated=1731354589" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-12-a1e58ad93c5f5e08b4cc458868cbc8d6</guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 21:14:45 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>The What is Money Show: Bitcoin is Money: The Language of Power with Robert Breedlove (WiM530)</title>
        <itunes:author>The What is Money Show</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords></itunes:keywords>
        <description>This episode discusses how money enhances trust and mirrors language, exploring Bitcoin&#39;s role as honest money. The conversation covers historical contexts of gold, central banking, and the evolving understanding of currency and power.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://cdn.simplecast.com/audio/2effec98-bec5-4728-ba08-7a86d776e682/episodes/126ba3c0-b932-4dc1-808f-6db480fc216b/audio/439cda70-db2e-44c4-81cd-c782990e1110/default_tc.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-12-571ce974c2be0e135d8fb93b5525b16f</guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 21:14:45 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Access Tribes Bitcoin Podcast: AT77 - Jill Ford, Bitcoin for Incarcerated Women</title>
        <itunes:author>Access Tribes Bitcoin Podcast</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>Bitcoin education, incarceration, financial empowerment, risks of fiat currency</itunes:keywords>
        <description>Jill Ford shares her unique journey in the Bitcoin mining industry, stemming from her personal experiences with fiat currency while incarcerated. She advocates for educating others about Bitcoin and sound money, aiming to empower individuals to make informed financial choices. Jill strives to help particularly those affected by the fiat system, encouraging knowledge as a tool for financial independence.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://api.substack.com/feed/podcast/151442850/7cb88ae68bd79abd97d77f38164091c9.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-11-7de7282b93a3facbc65d4cc788a02ffb</guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 20:28:28 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Bitcoin for Millennials: How Bitcoin Startups Are Changing the Game | Mike Jarmuz | BFM098</title>
        <itunes:author>Bitcoin for Millennials</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>Bitcoin startups, investment strategies, Bitcoin adoption, future of technology</itunes:keywords>
        <description>Mike Jarmuz discusses the role of Bitcoin startups in the investment landscape, emphasizing early-stage investing and funding strategies for founders. He highlights the current state of Bitcoin adoption and the evolution of Lightning Ventures, while exploring the future potential of Bitcoin companies across various industries. The conversation addresses challenges and opportunities in Bitcoin investing and the regulatory landscape&#39;s impact on growth.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://anchor.fm/s/e82b7a08/podcast/play/92314219/https%3A%2F%2Fd3ctxlq1ktw2nl.cloudfront.net%2Fstaging%2F2024-8-28%2F387199230-44100-2-1fcb1e7603cc6.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-11-7c0165f5c240012c0981b112b2007679</guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 20:28:28 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Coin Stories: Lyn Alden on Bitcoin Price Jump &amp; Future of Bitcoin: Navigating Forks, Risks, &amp; Institutional Impact</title>
        <itunes:author>Coin Stories</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>Bitcoin consensus, institutional investment, Bitcoin forks, market risks</itunes:keywords>
        <description>Lyn Alden discusses Bitcoin consensus, the risks linked to network fragmentation, and the influence of institutional investors on Bitcoin&#39;s future. She emphasizes the importance of education within the community regarding these complex dynamics and reviews the implications of recent events like Bitcoin&#39;s price reaching all-time highs. Together with her co-authors, she provides insights from their research on Bitcoin consensus and its associated risks.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://traffic.libsyn.com/secure/coinstories/208_Lyn_Alden_Consensus_Paper.mp3?dest-id=2813255" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-11-6cfecbe30f872d80e5afbd6eac1c4b96</guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 20:28:28 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Fractal Bitcoin: Bitcoin ATH melting faces approaching $90K LFG!!! Governments front running?</title>
        <itunes:author>Fractal Bitcoin</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>Bitcoin price movement, government policies, market implications, bullish sentiment</itunes:keywords>
        <description>This episode highlights Bitcoin&#39;s recent surge in price as it approaches an all-time high, while analysts predict potential increases up to $1 million. The discussion also critiques government monetary policies, with optimism conveyed through Bernstein research urging purchases of Bitcoin and crypto investments. The insights provided reflect on the dynamic relationship between Bitcoin and global political landscapes.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://podcasts.captivate.fm/media/0c2a9e1d-6d99-41ab-8b38-0a9e3cafe29b/218-Fractal-Bitcoin-2024-11-11-Bitcoin-ATH-melting-faces-approa.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-11-22c33283d194033016aa51e7c57f0fce</guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 20:28:28 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>POD256 Mining News: 057. From Sweden to Silicon: Bitcoin&#39;s Global Journey</title>
        <itunes:author>POD256 Mining News</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>Bitcoin community, mining innovations, political landscape, collaborative projects</itunes:keywords>
        <description>Recorded live, this episode features discussions about Bitcoin mining, community engagement, and innovative projects like the Ember One aimed at accessible mining. It includes personal stories from guests and humor regarding the current Bitcoin price debate, while also reflecting on political influences on cryptocurrency. The episode emphasizes collaboration and the community spirit driving the Bitcoin ecosystem forward.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://serve.podhome.fm/episode/e376190c-ff4b-4f09-e96a-08dc849e096d/63866942432553336748c86f30-fab3-41d6-8169-88f9e9ec060bv1.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-11-dbd5057a77a57a7a65ef2da314d66eab</guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 20:28:28 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Pleb Underground: Trumps Real Bitcoin Agenda Exposed! | Guest: BitcoinShooter | EP 111</title>
        <itunes:author>Pleb Underground</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>Trump presidency, Bitcoin influence, storytelling in Bitcoin, market trends</itunes:keywords>
        <description>BitcoinShooter joins to discuss his upcoming project while exploring the controversial link between the Trump presidency and Bitcoin. The conversation touches on how Bitcoin affects global conflicts, storytelling&#39;s role in the cryptocurrency narrative, and market trends related to political figures. The episode reflects on the implications of Trump&#39;s influence on the Bitcoin landscape and upcoming events.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://anchor.fm/s/add2abc4/podcast/play/94166483/https%3A%2F%2Fd3ctxlq1ktw2nl.cloudfront.net%2Fstaging%2F2024-10-8%2F389498398-44100-2-3f80ce6d6edd5.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-11-fb258bbf214463098700f34270de2a11</guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 20:28:28 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Robin Seyer: AVOID Costly Mistakes! The BEST Way to Keep Your BTC Safe</title>
        <itunes:author>Robin Seyer</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>Bitcoin self-custody, security practices, wallet management, educational insights</itunes:keywords>
        <description>This episode emphasizes the importance of self-custody for Bitcoin owners, as Robin Seyer discusses various security strategies including multi-signature and UTXO management. With practical takeaways, they highlight the necessity for users to understand their wallets to safeguard their investments effectively. Education is noted as a crucial factor in overcoming fears associated with self-custody.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://anchor.fm/s/ed1174c8/podcast/play/94056496/https%3A%2F%2Fd3ctxlq1ktw2nl.cloudfront.net%2Fstaging%2F2024-10-6%2F389362772-44100-2-002513ed9567.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-11-57dbb583744c44cb140e1c9671420e1b</guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 20:28:28 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Simply Bitcoin: BITCOIN BREAKS ALL TIME HIGH - What&#39;s Next? | EP 1116</title>
        <itunes:author>Simply Bitcoin</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>Bitcoin price surge, market speculation, future prospects, bull market</itunes:keywords>
        <description>This episode celebrates Bitcoin reaching an all-time high, surpassing $84,000, and discusses the potential for continued growth in the market. The hosts speculate on the implications of this bullish trend for the upcoming year, highlighting the significance of this development for Bitcoin&#39;s future prospects. </description>
        <enclosure url="https://anchor.fm/s/717a2198/podcast/play/94281735/https%3A%2F%2Fd3ctxlq1ktw2nl.cloudfront.net%2Fstaging%2F2024-10-11%2Fd8cb10cf-81c5-10df-3ecb-b92eb40efbc0.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-11-8bbb6b87519b982f7fa597bd27039300</guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 20:28:28 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Stephan Livera Podcast: Shaping Bitcoin&#39;s Future in UK with Freddie New SLP614</title>
        <itunes:author>Stephan Livera Podcast</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>Bitcoin regulation, UK policy, custodianship, political engagement</itunes:keywords>
        <description>Freddie New discusses the evolution of Bitcoin regulation in the UK, including challenges from the Financial Conduct Authority and recent policy shifts recognizing Bitcoin as property. He stresses the importance of engaging with politicians to foster a Bitcoin-friendly regulatory environment. The episode also covers issues such as fraud concerns impacting banking access and the potential for renewable energy in Bitcoin mining.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://anchor.fm/s/7d083a4/podcast/play/94247610/https%3A%2F%2Fd3ctxlq1ktw2nl.cloudfront.net%2Fstaging%2F2024-10-11%2F389599191-44100-2-4066475c631d5.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-11-1af8faa9cc985388c1dac772dfac109d</guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 20:28:28 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>TFTC A Bitcoin Podcast: #555: How Trump Will Serve The CBDC Agenda with Whitney Webb &amp; Mark Goodwin</title>
        <itunes:author>TFTC A Bitcoin Podcast</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>Trump policies, CBDC implications, Bitcoin influence, political narratives</itunes:keywords>
        <description>A discussion with Whitney Webb and Mark Goodwin reveals insights into Trump&#39;s connections to centralized digital currencies and the implications for Bitcoin. Key topics include the Trump coalition&#39;s dynamics, stablecoins, and the overall influence of politicians on crypto policies. The conversation scrutinizes the narrative around Trump as a supposed savior within the Bitcoin community.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://anchor.fm/s/558f520/podcast/play/94243179/https%3A%2F%2Fd3ctxlq1ktw2nl.cloudfront.net%2Fstaging%2F2024-10-11%2F389592746-44100-2-88eb12f6e4e6c.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-11-1624e9dfc1a5a2a1076a7a40ce7655ae</guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 20:28:28 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>The Bible and Bitcoin Podcast: Trump, the Great Awakening and the Refounding of America W/ The Based Boomer</title>
        <itunes:author>The Bible and Bitcoin Podcast</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>Great Awakening, faith and finance, Bitcoin advantages, community building</itunes:keywords>
        <description>This episode discusses the Great Awakening&#39;s implications for America, emphasizing the need for financial freedom and the negative effects of fiat currency. The hosts underscore the importance of community and education in navigating faith and finance discussions, advocating for Bitcoin as a solution to societal issues. </description>
        <enclosure url="https://mcdn.podbean.com/mf/web/fqph4qnhf45g5zqb/1110.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-11-09e758f026e875228c398d5f6af29840</guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 20:28:28 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>The Breakdown: The Present and Future of Crypto-Based Prediction Markets</title>
        <itunes:author>The Breakdown</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>Prediction markets, decentralized finance, market trends, technological advancements</itunes:keywords>
        <description>This episode explores the rise of crypto-based prediction markets, discussing their operation and potential impact on traditional markets. Insights center on decentralized finance&#39;s role in their growth and various application areas. The conversation highlights present trends, challenges, and opportunities in this evolving sector.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://traffic.megaphone.fm/BWG8169627216.mp3?updated=1731362777" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-11-8d27c29db3703f82b59bb56559196d15</guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 20:28:28 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>The Bugle Weekly: Selection Autopsy | Bugle Weekly Episode 34</title>
        <itunes:author>The Bugle Weekly</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>Bitcoin news, cryptocurrency developments, market implications, recent updates</itunes:keywords>
        <description>The hosts cover the most significant Bitcoin news from the past week, providing updates on notable developments in the cryptocurrency market. The discussion aims to keep Bitcoin enthusiasts informed about the implications these updates may have for the future of Bitcoin.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://media.rss.com/bugle/2024_11_11_16_16_34_2f62f00a-070a-45c5-bef5-a048da778ddd.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-11-d42095edb9432bed5fc24f162c3caf4d</guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 20:28:28 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>The Davani Connection: TDC #243: POWER ANALYSIS OF BITCOIN - with JAMES CHECK</title>
        <itunes:author>The Davani Connection</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>On-chain data analysis, Bitcoin market conditions, investor psychology, expert insights</itunes:keywords>
        <description>James Check provides expert insights into Bitcoin&#39;s on-chain data, merging data interpretation with an understanding of investor psychology to analyze market conditions. This episode serves as an in-depth discussion of the factors influencing Bitcoin&#39;s price and market behavior, offering listeners a nuanced perspective on current trends.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://anchor.fm/s/ada8e8c/podcast/play/94248928/https%3A%2F%2Fd3ctxlq1ktw2nl.cloudfront.net%2Fstaging%2F2024-10-11%2F9586d485-645b-bcf5-2283-03a6ba8727ff.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-11-033cb998e55f365e0fa7532350c5711b</guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 20:28:28 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>This Week in Bitcoin: Why the Market is High on Bitcoin</title>
        <itunes:author>This Week in Bitcoin</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>Bitcoin market surge, ETF developments, investing strategies, market implications</itunes:keywords>
        <description>The episode examines the factors contributing to the recent surge in Bitcoin prices and its impact on stock markets. It discusses the growth in assets within US spot Bitcoin ETFs and their significance. Additionally, the hosts cover recent Bitcoin-related developments and their implications for investors&#39; strategies moving forward.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://op3.dev/e/serve.podhome.fm/episode/f01a19c0-6f9d-4aef-9515-08dc15242149/638669585857345862edb29d64-55a5-46f9-8872-2d5cd618a8eav1.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-11-f6208d98bf7d45101c758ec81383669d</guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 20:28:28 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Token Metrics Daily Podcast: Crypto Bull SZN is live! ARE YOU IN?</title>
        <itunes:author>Token Metrics Daily Podcast</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>Crypto market trends, Solana performance, legal battles in crypto, market excitement</itunes:keywords>
        <description>This episode highlights the excitement surrounding the crypto market&#39;s recent performance, noting a consistent six-day surge. The hosts discuss Solana&#39;s remarkable rise to a significant market cap and touch on the ongoing legal challenges faced by FTX. The tone is optimistic, reflecting the current bullish sentiment in the market. </description>
        <enclosure url="https://www.buzzsprout.com/2224561/episodes/16083744-crypto-bull-szn-is-live-are-you-in.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-11-1046e7674143f20f8738c8e686c98f67</guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 20:28:28 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Bitcoin and Markets: ETF Options Approval and Central Bankers Attack Bitcoin With Nonsense - E410</title>
        <itunes:author>Bitcoin and Markets</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>[ETF options, Central banking rhetoric, Macroeconomic analysis, Importance of research]</itunes:keywords>
        <description>This episode discusses ETF options approval and strategies used by central bankers to undermine Bitcoin. It analyzes macroeconomic factors affecting Bitcoin and critiques traditional financial institutions&#39; rhetoric. The episode stresses the importance of conducting independent research amidst financial misinformation.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/pscrb.fm/rss/p/traffic.libsyn.com/secure/bitcoinandmarkets/e410.mp3?dest-id=1230017" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-09-d6f410433ddde26b54a3bb5ce7e49c60</guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 07:57:02 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Bitcoin Audible: Chat 117-Bitcoin Threat Vectors on Final Settlement</title>
        <itunes:author>Bitcoin Audible</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>[Bitcoin custody, Security challenges, Multisig setups, Personal security incident]</itunes:keywords>
        <description>This episode covers Bitcoin custodial threat vectors and the unique security challenges associated with it. Insights from a personal security incident highlight the real risks faced by Bitcoin holders. The discussion includes the evolution of custody solutions and the importance of multisig setups for securing assets.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://episodes.castos.com/6626b866f2af87-36468692/1878430/c1e-q7pqji280p1f7n7d9-rkdk607gczg9-fiy2jf.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-09-363cca346c62d4476e09a04ed1398730</guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 07:57:02 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>BTC Sessions: WHY ARE WE BULLISH? David Branscum, Aladdin (BTC Cards), Nathan Fitzsimmons (The BTC Mentor) ep251</title>
        <itunes:author>BTC Sessions</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>[Bullish sentiment, Investment strategies, Self-custody, Hardware wallets]</itunes:keywords>
        <description>This episode features a discussion on the bullish sentiment surrounding Bitcoin, focusing on investment strategies and self-custody. Guests share their experiences with hardware wallets and the implications of Bitcoin&#39;s market behavior. The conversation emphasizes the importance of privacy and secure engagement with Bitcoin.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://anchor.fm/s/11e95d20/podcast/play/94169263/https%3A%2F%2Fd3ctxlq1ktw2nl.cloudfront.net%2Fstaging%2F2024-10-9%2Fddaa9f83-a2c4-85a4-8f74-9ae887ad37b9.m4a" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-09-f27b4663317cbb7541f07d29f73078d3</guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 07:57:02 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Coin Stories: &#39;News Block: Bitcoin Enters Price Discovery After Trump Win, Fed Cuts Rates Again, Bond Yields Rise Amid Inflation Fears&#39;</title>
        <itunes:author>Coin Stories</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>[Price discovery, Political impact, Institutional adoption, Economic trends]</itunes:keywords>
        <description>This episode covers critical news affecting Bitcoin, including its record highs following Trump&#39;s re-election and pro-crypto candidates winning congressional seats. It also discusses the Federal Reserve&#39;s rate cuts and their implications for Bitcoin alongside institutional adoption trends. The episode analyzes investment movements and Bitcoin&#39;s current economic environment.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://traffic.libsyn.com/secure/coinstories/307_61_NewsBlock_Nat.mp3?dest-id=2813255" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-09-7cf8945ac2ba3f0c051b07bd7d03b705</guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 07:57:02 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Fractal Bitcoin: Bitcoin 3rd day all-time highs! $420K in 2025?! Global FOMO incoming! - Ep.217</title>
        <itunes:author>Fractal Bitcoin</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>[Price discovery, ETF growth, Historical comparisons, Government adoption]</itunes:keywords>
        <description>This episode highlights Bitcoin&#39;s recent price activity, suggesting an ambitious price projection of $420,000 by 2025 amid a surge in ETF assets. It compares Bitcoin&#39;s adoption to the internet&#39;s growth and discusses significant developments in municipal acceptance of cryptocurrencies for tax payments. Noteworthy events include record purchases by Bitcoin ETFs.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://podcasts.captivate.fm/media/49a9d7c1-2716-4a9f-ac7b-7832619173d5/217-Fractal-Bitcoin-2024-11-08-Bitcoin-3rd-day-all-time-highs-4.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-09-aa796bad9f281d39002a298826e2a1cc</guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 07:57:02 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Onramp Media: &#39;The Last Trade E073: The Orange Wave with Larry Lepard &amp; David Foley&#39;</title>
        <itunes:author>Onramp Media</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>[Election impact, Bitcoin reserves, Monetary policy, Institutional strategies]</itunes:keywords>
        <description>This episode discusses the intersection of Bitcoin and upcoming election dynamics, emphasizing the potential for a pro-Bitcoin administration. Topics include the idea of a Strategic Bitcoin Reserve and the role of sound assets in today’s economy. The discussion includes market insights and comparisons between Bitcoin and gold.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://anchor.fm/s/e01a5d48/podcast/play/94144964/https%3A%2F%2Fd3ctxlq1ktw2nl.cloudfront.net%2Fstaging%2F2024-10-8%2F389471753-44100-2-dc2acdf376635.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-09-ab2254d1ac56507442131746132698a9</guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 07:57:02 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Pleb Underground: Bitcoin Mining CRISIS On The Horizon?</title>
        <itunes:author>Pleb Underground</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>[Bitcoin mining crisis, Cost implications, Resource allocation, Profitability concerns]</itunes:keywords>
        <description>This episode explores a looming crisis in Bitcoin mining as operational costs rise and profits decline. Hosts discuss resource shifts towards AI and the financial viability of Bitcoin mining operations. The discussion provides insights into current trends and challenges faced by miners in the cryptocurrency landscape.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://anchor.fm/s/add2abc4/podcast/play/94169424/https%3A%2F%2Fd3ctxlq1ktw2nl.cloudfront.net%2Fstaging%2F2024-10-9%2F389502020-44100-2-9158645eb7646.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-09-3fcc4e2a40fa721fb078c96ab2a86969</guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 07:57:02 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Robin Seyer: &#39;Trillion-Dollar BTC Bet: Microstrategy Soon Biggest Firm in the world?&#39;</title>
        <itunes:author>Robin Seyer</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>[MicroStrategy&#39;s Bitcoin strategy, Future of finance, Bitcoin as a commodity, Educational accessibility]</itunes:keywords>
        <description>Tim Kotzman discusses Bitcoin&#39;s transformative potential through MicroStrategy&#39;s significant investments, suggesting it could evolve into a trillion-dollar entity. The episode highlights Bitcoin as a commodity and emphasizes the need for accessible channels for engaging with cryptocurrency. It positions MicroStrategy at the forefront of Bitcoin&#39;s integration into the broader economy.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://anchor.fm/s/ed1174c8/podcast/play/93963409/https%3A%2F%2Fd3ctxlq1ktw2nl.cloudfront.net%2Fstaging%2F2024-10-4%2F389246724-44100-2-b067ffb217345.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-09-7579b366a568fd7b586553212a756117</guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 07:57:02 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Simply Bitcoin: &#39;BREAKING: Central Banker EXPOSED In BOMBSHELL Interview | EP 1115&#39;</title>
        <itunes:author>Simply Bitcoin</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>[Central banking policies, Monetary implications, Financial landscape, Inflation]</itunes:keywords>
        <description>This episode discusses controversial remarks made by Jerome Powell concerning central banking practices and their ramifications for the economy. The analysis focuses on the future of digital currencies and the implications of monetary policies on Bitcoin and inflationary concerns. This disclosure is contextualized against current economic challenges.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://anchor.fm/s/717a2198/podcast/play/94158233/https%3A%2F%2Fd3ctxlq1ktw2nl.cloudfront.net%2Fstaging%2F2024-10-8%2Fe85e7f81-f206-0540-74ad-aa5165431a58.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-09-e206ae5be87623a8c2dbaf2c8a1bdeaf</guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 07:57:02 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Swan Signal Live A Bitcoin Show: Is This the Start of a Super Cycle?</title>
        <itunes:author>Swan Signal Live A Bitcoin Show</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>[Market trends, Policy impact, Government support, Price projections]</itunes:keywords>
        <description>The discussion revolves around Bitcoin&#39;s performance following Trump&#39;s election, with a focus on potential new price highs and the possibility of a &quot;super cycle.&quot; It examines expected government policies favorable to Bitcoin, including potential strategic reserves. The episode captures a sense of optimism about Bitcoin&#39;s mainstream acceptance.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://cdn.simplecast.com/audio/6b4113f8-61fd-4976-a3e6-4d8ed2143233/episodes/66c8eb04-aad5-4762-a7e7-a6ff764b45a7/audio/7db6bc1b-31ed-4638-9ed1-87221b7150db/default_tc.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-09-6a6e060bcd4cf19752027aa289a579c5</guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 07:57:02 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>TFTC A Bitcoin Podcast: &#39;#554: UAP Disclosure Is Upon Us with Matt Pines&#39;</title>
        <itunes:author>TFTC A Bitcoin Podcast</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>[UAP disclosure, Bitcoin policy, Supranational institutions, Geopolitical insight]</itunes:keywords>
        <description>This episode with Matt Pines discusses the potential inclusion of Bitcoin in Trump&#39;s policy amidst an impending UAP disclosure. It covers the evolution of supranational financial institutions, American geopolitical power, and the implications of technology in current defense strategies. Key insights highlight the intersections between these areas and Bitcoin&#39;s future.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://anchor.fm/s/558f520/podcast/play/94118870/https%3A%2F%2Fd3ctxlq1ktw2nl.cloudfront.net%2Fstaging%2F2024-10-7%2F389439343-44100-2-9e27664ca37c4.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-09-1175a2dd9632d69e35355d44bf9ba245</guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 07:57:02 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>The Mark Moss Show: China Fires A Monetary Bazooka... Will It Be Enough?</title>
        <itunes:author>The Mark Moss Show</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>[China&#39;s financial strategy, Global market impact, Bitcoin implications, Investment strategies]</itunes:keywords>
        <description>Analyzing China&#39;s dramatic financial maneuvers, this episode questions the potential effects on global markets, including U.S. stocks and Bitcoin. Historical insights into past economic strategies provide context for current events. The discussion emphasizes the need for investment positioning in the wake of these developments.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://chtbl.com/track/5899E/podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/pscrb.fm/rss/p/traffic.omny.fm/d/clips/e73c998e-6e60-432f-8610-ae210140c5b1/7abcd9bc-1b66-4c1e-a89b-ae3c000322cc/58919d90-21e3-4fa0-8970-b22201811bef/audio.mp3?utm_source=Podcast&in_playlist=9acb2eb4-8765-4a8a-8a57-ae3c000322da" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-09-e02805fe36a4d20f0fce82e52ea7c107</guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 07:57:02 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>The Transformation of Value: What is Nuclear Energy with Nick Touran</title>
        <itunes:author>The Transformation of Value</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>[Nuclear energy, Political challenges, Economic implications, Regulatory landscape]</itunes:keywords>
        <description>This episode features a discussion with nuclear engineer Nick Touran about the challenges and opportunities facing the nuclear energy sector. The conversation covers the history of nuclear energy, its current regulatory issues, and the outlook for future technology in energy production and abundance.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://anchor.fm/s/d48d2ca8/podcast/play/94135276/https%3A%2F%2Fd3ctxlq1ktw2nl.cloudfront.net%2Fstaging%2F2024-10-8%2Fb7b6dca5-c70b-1184-8541-982ef2ce72b7.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-09-9321da2b50c1bbb1ce1477a449e1cbd0</guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 07:57:02 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>The What is Money Show: Can Trump Save the West? Freedom, Peterson vs. Dawkins, COVID &amp; Bitcoin w/ Bret Weinstein (WiM529)</title>
        <itunes:author>The What is Money Show</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>[Incentives in evolution, Libertarianism, Technology in academia, Freedom vs. tyranny]</itunes:keywords>
        <description>Dr. Bret Weinstein discusses the interplay of incentives in evolution and the relevance of Libertarianism to contemporary society, along with the potential impacts of Trump on freedom and governance. The dialogue explores major cultural debates, including the discourse surrounding COVID-19 mandates and their implications for societal values.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://cdn.simplecast.com/audio/2effec98-bec5-4728-ba08-7a86d776e682/episodes/fbe9659d-6735-4ccd-847b-7989b8eb4460/audio/ddd283fc-e95f-494d-a880-a57c48878ba2/default_tc.mp3?aid=rss_feed&feed=MLdpYXYI" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-09-820078ecbf5a2e8224037b2d5dad12ab</guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 07:57:02 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Token Metrics Daily Podcast: Rate Down, Crypto Up, BTC Tax📊</title>
        <itunes:author>Token Metrics Daily Podcast</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>[Fed rate decision, Crypto market response, Urban crypto adoption, Timeliness of information]</itunes:keywords>
        <description>This episode discusses the positive response of the crypto market to the US Federal Reserve&#39;s rate decision, alongside a focus on a US city significantly embracing cryptocurrency. The conversation highlights the role of crypto in improving public awareness of financial events.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://www.buzzsprout.com/2224561/episodes/16070362-rate-down-crypto-up-btc-tax.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-11-09-2028200e8b077474c23fdf429942979a</guid>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 07:57:02 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>
