<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>
<title>The Hodljuice Daily Pint</title>
<link>https://hodljuice.app</link>
<language>en-us</language>
<itunes:author>curated by Hodljuice</itunes:author>
<description>Daily collection of various Bitcoin-related podcasts</description>
<itunes:category text="Technology">
</itunes:category>
<itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:owner>
<itunes:name>Hodljuice</itunes:name>
<itunes:email>hodljuice@hodljuice.app</itunes:email>
</itunes:owner>
<image>
<url>https://hodljuice.app/static/icon-512x512.png</url>
<title>The Hodljuice Daily Pint</title>
<link>https://hodljuice.app</link>
</image>
<lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 20:36:35 CST</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
        <title>Bitcorner with Juan Cienfuegos: &quot;Khushboo Khullar: About Adopting Bitcoin, Lightning Ventures, and Thunder Funder&quot;</title>
        <itunes:author>Bitcorner with Juan Cienfuegos</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>Bitcoin adoption, startup funding, Lightning Ventures, community connections</itunes:keywords>
        <description>Khushboo Khullar from Lightning Ventures discusses the importance of Bitcoin adoption and its effect on global acceptance. She explores the platform Thunder Funder, which aims to democratize investments in Bitcoin startups. The episode also highlights the relationship between Bitcoin, energy security, and nation-state reserves. Khushboo shares her personal journey and the significance of community in the Bitcoin ecosystem.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://api.substack.com/feed/podcast/152400929/f3657d19975677c5a6d027a475310cb1.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-12-03-2d8964ff2baf92e75162256a2078f672</guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 20:36:35 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Coin Stories: &#39;Luke Gromen: Bitcoin as &quot;The New Oil,&quot; Trump&amp;#39;s Tariffs, and the Death of the Dollar-Centric System&#39;</title>
        <itunes:author>Coin Stories</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>Macro economics, Bitcoin valuation, geopolitical implications, Trump&#39;s economic policies</itunes:keywords>
        <description>In this episode, Luke Gromen shares his macroeconomic outlook and discusses the implications of Bitcoin being considered &quot;the new oil.&quot; He covers topics such as Trump&#39;s economic strategies, the strengthening dollar, and Bitcoin&#39;s potential as a strategic asset. The conversation also addresses how tariffs are affecting global markets and hints at Bitcoin’s massive potential for future growth.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://traffic.libsyn.com/secure/coinstories/315_Luke_Gromen.mp3?dest-id=2813255" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-12-03-299d54e86f02f4ff4c657bede12a14ce</guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 20:36:35 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Fractal Bitcoin: Bitcoin Update! Pump Soon. US Dollar Collapse Update! BlackRock’s 500,000 BTC - Ep. 225</title>
        <itunes:author>Fractal Bitcoin</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>Bitcoin price predictions, ETF developments, digital currency concerns, investment security</itunes:keywords>
        <description>This episode anticipates a surge in Bitcoin&#39;s price and discusses the recent milestone where a spot ETF has exceeded 500,000 Bitcoin in assets under management. The conversation includes Virgin Voyages becoming a pioneer in Bitcoin payment acceptance and the risks associated with increased government involvement in cryptocurrency. Listeners are urged to secure their Bitcoin outside exchanges.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://podcasts.captivate.fm/media/bdb1b0c9-700e-44c0-ac3b-3569e7bb4af1/225-Fractal-Bitcoin-2024-12-03-Bitcoin-Update-Pump-Soon-US-Doll.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-12-03-68e196bcc8710f011c11c45385506566</guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 20:36:35 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Pleb Underground: The FIRST Bitcoin Bear Market Indicators of This Cycle</title>
        <itunes:author>Pleb Underground</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>Market cycles, investment indicators, Bitcoin&#39;s future, financial advice</itunes:keywords>
        <description>The episode discusses early indicators of an impending Bitcoin bear market, cautioning listeners against complacency despite current bullish trends. Essential topics include potential downturns, implications of pending legislation, and the consequences of the Federal Reserve&#39;s interest rate adjustments. The hosts advise staying informed and vigilant as market conditions change.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://anchor.fm/s/add2abc4/podcast/play/95258750/https%3A%2F%2Fd3ctxlq1ktw2nl.cloudfront.net%2Fstaging%2F2024-11-2%2F390849970-44100-2-8e692597b3a31.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-12-03-4cde82e3e2588b6578f67ed859004813</guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 20:36:35 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Robin Seyer: &#39;The Big Investment Lie: Why Bitcoin is Your Only Choice!&#39;</title>
        <itunes:author>Robin Seyer</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>Behavioral analysis, autism and finance, delayed gratification, barriers to Bitcoin adoption</itunes:keywords>
        <description>Dillon Ganesh discusses the intersection of behavioral analysis and Bitcoin, emphasizing the importance of saving and the role of delayed gratification in financial success. He addresses common misconceptions about Bitcoin and the barriers to its adoption, advocating for education and understanding its value. The episode envisions a future where Bitcoin empowers individuals through financial security.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://anchor.fm/s/ed1174c8/podcast/play/95177641/https%3A%2F%2Fd3ctxlq1ktw2nl.cloudfront.net%2Fstaging%2F2024-10-30%2F390752682-44100-2-89ead7327c235.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-12-03-1b12f4804b9f17580c6b63028c22dd30</guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 20:36:35 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>Simply Bitcoin: Will Bitcoin Make Microsoft the Next Microstrategy? | EP 1131</title>
        <itunes:author>Simply Bitcoin</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>Corporate Bitcoin strategy, financial implications, market perception, risk assessment</itunes:keywords>
        <description>The hosts explore the potential for Microsoft to adopt a Bitcoin acquisition strategy similar to Microstrategy, analyzing the financial motivations and market implications. They discuss the risks and rewards involved in such a strategic move, highlighting the effect on both corporations and the cryptocurrency market. The conversation emphasizes Bitcoin&#39;s growing importance in corporate financial planning.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://anchor.fm/s/717a2198/podcast/play/95313065/https%3A%2F%2Fd3ctxlq1ktw2nl.cloudfront.net%2Fstaging%2F2024-11-3%2F71e1593c-e044-95e0-2657-f0d9eee69aa4.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-12-03-8420c2c084d5717537d5ec3c4714f22d</guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 20:36:35 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>The Bitcoin Frontier: What happens after $100,000 bitcoin? Willy Woo’s first interview in 3 years</title>
        <itunes:author>The Bitcoin Frontier</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>Bitcoin market analysis, institutional impact, energy scarcity, geopolitical implications</itunes:keywords>
        <description>Willy Woo provides an insightful analysis of the Bitcoin market, discussing the influence of major players like MicroStrategy and BlackRock. He outlines Bitcoin’s potential to become a global reserve asset, its energy scarcity model, and how new accounting standards could impact corporate holdings. The episode explores Bitcoin&#39;s role in reshaping global monetary systems and geopolitical landscapes.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://media.transistor.fm/a81291c0/296365f8.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-12-03-4edd841fa42553260a45a25087285811</guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 20:36:35 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>The Bitcoin Standard Podcast: 250. Fiat Architecture and Time Preference</title>
        <itunes:author>The Bitcoin Standard Podcast</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>Economic behavior, fiat currency influence, time preference</itunes:keywords>
        <description>In this episode, the discussion revolves around how fiat currency shapes societal structure and individual economic behavior through its effects on time preference. The guests analyze the implications of easy money on architecture and broader economic systems. The conversation critiques current monetary policies and emphasizes the need for alternative models.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://www.buzzsprout.com/1849151/episodes/16213100-250-fiat-architecture-and-time-preference.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-12-03-aa845cdb59084a56a55ded6ee6fcb805</guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 20:36:35 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>The Block Reward Bitcoin For Beginners: &#39;62: Ryan Macleod ON: The Synergy Of Bitcoin Mining and Nuclear Power&#39;</title>
        <itunes:author>The Block Reward Bitcoin For Beginners</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>Nuclear energy, Bitcoin mining integration, energy challenges, technological advancements</itunes:keywords>
        <description>Ryan MacLeod discusses the synergy between Bitcoin mining and nuclear power, highlighting how nuclear energy could meet Bitcoin’s energy demands and benefit power grids. The discussion includes challenges, opportunities in public perception, and advancements in both sectors. He also discusses the concept of transforming waste energy into value through Bitcoin mining.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://audio-delivery.cohostpodcasting.com/audio/99707283-ab68-4240-9fff-177a3f522270/episodes/328609ab-b7e7-40b6-939b-da6155b97f06/episode.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-12-03-93f64022fa95f37012c425967552bb9e</guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 20:36:35 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>The Mining Pod: Block’s New ASIC Miner With Core Scientific and Proto</title>
        <itunes:author>The Mining Pod</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>ASIC mining technology, industry collaboration, market dynamics, geopolitical factors</itunes:keywords>
        <description>In this episode, The Mining Pod discusses the collaboration between Proto and Core Scientific on new ASIC chip technology designed for Bitcoin mining. The hosts cover the advantages of developing ASICs, the competitive landscape of the industry, and geopolitical influences affecting the market. The episode also explores future technological advancements and market interests in US-made ASICs.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/SSYDL1642390558.mp3?updated=1733194818" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-12-03-3115053f9953b9785242021db80dfe11</guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 20:36:35 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>The Mining Pod: Cleanspark FY2024 Earnings Call Analysis</title>
        <itunes:author>The Mining Pod</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>Financial performance, market trends, bitcoin mining stocks</itunes:keywords>
        <description>This episode analyzes Cleanspark&#39;s FY2024 earnings call, with insights from analysts on the company’s financial performance and its implications for the Bitcoin mining industry. The discussion covers key market trends impacting mining stocks and includes expert opinions from industry leaders. Listeners are encouraged to find more details on these insights through additional platforms.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://www.podtrac.com/pts/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/SSYDL5100484438.mp3?updated=1733193944" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-12-03-71987139a69d54f5b13b8d4a35f95376</guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 20:36:35 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>The What is Money Show: Breaking Out of the Money Printing Mind Control with Dad Saves America (WiM536)</title>
        <itunes:author>The What is Money Show</itunes:author>
        <itunes:keywords>Inflation critique, Keynesian economics, integrity in finance, familial perspectives</itunes:keywords>
        <description>John Papola discusses the nature of money, criticizing the inflationary practices inherent in current economic systems and equating money printing to mind control. He examines how these economic policies affect societal integrity and the significance of fatherhood in modern discourse. The episode critiques Keynesian economics and emphasizes the importance of responsible financial practices.</description>
        <enclosure url="https://cdn.simplecast.com/audio/2effec98-bec5-4728-ba08-7a86d776e682/episodes/cc53ba42-2658-49bb-8b85-5d9b5c293fe6/audio/8ec1c24e-ff2a-4afd-a2bd-e922c408d1b4/default_tc.mp3?aid=rss_feed&feed=MLdpYXYI" type="audio/mpeg" length="0" />
        <guid isPermaLink="false">hodljuice-2024-12-03-4c330eb18481514bcfed2e8b3052d4ec</guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 20:36:35 CST</pubDate>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>
